<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lucas Myers on</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Lucas Myers on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://lucasmyers97.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Latex</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/latex/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:08:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/latex/</guid><description>Custom commands To add a custom command, use the \newcommand command
1 \newcommand{\R}{\mathbb{R}}</description></item><item><title>Python</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/python/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 11:06:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/python/</guid><description>Installing vanilla python To use ipython and jupyter I needed to install the appropriate packages:
1 2 3 4 sudo apt-get install build-essential gdb lcov pkg-config \ libbz2-dev libffi-dev libgdbm-dev libgdbm-compat-dev liblzma-dev \ libncurses5-dev libreadline6-dev libsqlite3-dev libssl-dev \ lzma lzma-dev tk-dev uuid-dev zlib1g-dev A list can also be found here in the python dev guides.</description></item><item><title>Paraview</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/paraview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 11:06:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/paraview/</guid><description>Programmable filter See here for documentation
Basic input/output 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 vector_data = inputs[0].PointData[&amp;#39;vector_data&amp;#39;] scalar_data = inputs[0].</description></item><item><title>Neovim</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/neovim/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 14:03:29 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/neovim/</guid><description> Configuration files Foward and inverse latex search with Lua (coming soon, see this gist for an example config)</description></item><item><title>Todo</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/todo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 22:27:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/todo/</guid><description>Website Write post about easily creating documentation with Poxy using GitHub pages to deploy. Increase font size Figure out better organization Include CV Figure out Table of Contents Publish Fourier Widget to GitHub Write sidebar Make hamburger icon see here for tutorial Write &amp;ldquo;how to make a sidebar and toolbar post&amp;rdquo; New Website Start writing Quartz in Zola Professional stuff Update CV Add README&amp;rsquo;s to projects on GitHub Neovim Write post about find and replace in vim Figure out folding for comments Figure out folding for content Fix error with org stuff so I can continue to edit org files Figure out how to paste images from clipboard Figure out how to access clipboard images in Lua Put clipboard image in folder Figure out good way to specify which folder things are pasted into (potentially based on current and an image folder) In pasting images, automatically create link which goes to that image Figure out dap ( watch this).</description></item><item><title>JackTrip</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/jacktrip/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 22:10:38 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/jacktrip/</guid><description>Introduction Part of the issue with getting Jacktrip set up is that there are lots of resources floating around, many of which are extremely outdated.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/about_me/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:59:29 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/about_me/</guid><description>I am currently a PhD candidate in the physics department at the University of Minnesota studying soft matter. I tend to get obsessive about technical tasks, especially when they make promises of making other (menial) work easier or more enjoyable.</description></item><item><title>Posts</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/posts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:24:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/posts/</guid><description>Fourier series widget I wrote a widget which allows one to interactively watch a partial Fourier sum converge. In undergrad I was always sort of dubious that all functions (in $L_2$ space) could be represented by Fourier series, so I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this makes it a little bit more palatable.</description></item><item><title>Notes</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:06:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/notes/</guid><description> Todo Neovim C++ Python Paraview Linux Git Website Lua Lilypond Reaper (DAW) jacktrip Licensing Latex</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/projects/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 18:54:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/projects/</guid><description>Hydrodynamics of anisotropically elastic nematic liquid crystals Nematic liquid crystals are materials with rod-like particles which tend to align on macroscopic scales.</description></item><item><title>C++</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/c++/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/c++/</guid><description>Passing Lambda functions by reference See here for a clear explanation of what&amp;rsquo;s going on with the auto keyword. Apparently C++ Lambda functions are just syntactic sugar for callable objects (classes which implement the operator() function).</description></item><item><title>Doxygen</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/doxygen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/doxygen/</guid><description>Introduction Doxygen is a command-line utility which goes through code-bases and documents code based on (a) the code itself and (b) special comments that developers can make to include extra information.</description></item><item><title>Git</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/git/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/git/</guid><description>Tutorials Really slick space-themed Learn git branching is a cool Javascript-based tutorial which visually explains some intermediate aspects of git.</description></item><item><title>Licensing</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/licensing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/licensing/</guid><description>Introduction I am getting to a point where I will be releasing software so I should give my repos licenses, otherwise they cannot be used by other people.</description></item><item><title>Linux</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/linux/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/linux/</guid><description>Sound driver Getting headphone mic to work See reddit post and corresponding Arch linux wiki. Also on the Reddit page:</description></item><item><title>Lua</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/lua/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/lua/</guid><description>Installing Lua 5.1 (Neovim&amp;rsquo;s version) Here is a list of source versions. Download and do the checksum. Just as a reminder, the checksum is done with:</description></item><item><title>Neovim configuration</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/neovim_configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/neovim_configuration/</guid><description>Default neovim settings</description></item><item><title>Website</title><link>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucasmyers97.github.io/notes/website/</guid><description>Darkmode responsive Mermaid diagrams Mermaid is a utility for generating diagrams based on plain-text, typically through Markdown. It is supported by GitHub natively, and can create class diagrams, sequence diagrams, Gitgraphs, and more.</description></item></channel></rss>